Hirose?
You're not here for work, I take it.
Is everything all right?
Yes, what brings you here at this hour?
This.
You forgot your wallet at the auditorium.
I didn't receive a reply when I called,
so I thought to check your license,
and make the delivery myself.
I apologize for surprising you.
No, I'm sorry I made you go out of your way.
Mao... Tsukidome hurt his foot,
so I didn't notice your calls.
I only just finished treating him.
I'm terribly sorry for the trouble.
Don't worry, you caused no trouble at all.
Thank you so much.
I hear your birthday is next Thursday?
That's right.
Then we have to celebrate.
Absolutely!
I'm sorry, I actually have plans that day.
Oh?
"Plans," huh?
Not with a lover, of course.
He invited me to dinner
without knowing it was my birthday.
- Really?
- I see.
Sorry, I have plans Thursday.
Pencil me in for another day.
Thanks.
Mao.
Are you free next Thursday?
Huh?
My mother taught me her napolitan recipe,
and I wanted you to try.
Thursday...
Mao?
Yeah, I'm free.
Great!
Get ready to have your socks blown off,
I'll put my all into cooking for you.
Thanks, I will.
Mao.
How long have you been there?
Doesn't matter, right?
You scare me sometimes.
I hear Thursday is Monou's birthday.
- Really?
- Don't bother, I can tell you knew.
You said you'd treat Nana well.
I can trust you on that, right?
Of course.
If you realize you can't be there for her,
then I'm going after her myself.
I'm serious about her.
See you around.
[Obstetrics and gynecology]
Ms. Yamaguchi?
We're ready for you.
We meet again.
Getting another check up?
Hello! Yes, I am.
Is your due date coming up?
Yes. I'm expecting next month, on the 7th.
Boy or girl?
Girl.
I also have a daughter.
Though I've caused her nothing but trouble,
I'm truly glad she was born.
I'm itching to meet my child as well.
Babies are so wonderful.
Just seeing them makes everyone happy.
Ma'am, are you all right?
I'm sorry. Was I looking glum?
I've had to frequent the hospital these days,
and I worry I'm troubling my daughter...
I'm being quite the burden to her.
If I were in her shoes,
I wouldn't think you were a burden.
You are her mother.
Nothing would make your daughter happier
than seeing her mother healthy again.
You think so?
I do.
Thank you.
Of course.
Come into this world safely.
And you take care, dear.
Thank you.
Sis!
Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
It is almost your turn?
- "Sis"?
- I think I'm after this next patient.
Sounds good.
That's her younger sister?
Misaki.
Misaki?
Sorry, what's up?
Everything all right?
You seem tired.
I'm fine.
When do you think you'll be discharged?
The doctors say
I'll be let out early this time.
Really? I'm glad to hear it.
Is she packed for the hospital?
[Erika Katsuragawa]
She should get that prepped now.
I think she was, but...
- Rin.
- Yeah?
Are you packed for the hospital?
Yeah. My bags are by the front door.
Did you hear that?
I did.
She apparently feels too heavy to move.
That doesn't surprise me.
Can you pass the phone to Rin?
I promised to give her some baby supplies.
Sure.
- Here.
- Hello?
Hey, Erika.
'Sup.
How're you feeling?
Better these days.
Rin's really going to be a mom, isn't she...
All right, thanks.
Talk to you later.
Thanks.
I feel so heavy...
You okay?
Yeah. She had not been kicking,
maybe because it's tight in there?
But today she's moving like crazy.
She's happy you're here.
Must be because I help her mom take it easy.
We appreciate a sister we can rely on, right?
Rin looked overjoyed.
I'm happy for her.
Happiness comes in many forms.
But the joy she's acquired
is something very substantial.
Yeah.
I've thought about
whether I want a child or not.
But I don't know what it is I want,
no matter how much I ponder it.
I understand giving birth
may be difficult for me.
Even so, I can't definitively say
I don't want children.
I know.
Erika.
I expected to fall in love, get married,
and one day have a child,
like every other family.
But if I'm unable to conceive,
I'm depriving my future partner
of that opportunity.
If that's the consequence...
then I should give up on marriage.
I should give up on romance entirely.
I'm less bothered by the fact
that I can't give birth.
Rather, I'm more upset I can't give anyone
the happiness they'd expect from a family.
And yet, I...
Even though I know it's impossible, I...
Happiness is a difficult thing, isn't it?
Sui. There's something I haven't told you
because I didn't want you to judge us.
My husband was also infertile.
The doctors said our chances
were practically zero.
But I never once thought of leaving him.
I love my husband, first and foremost.
Children was only an option, not a necessity.
My husband...
Although he was told our chances were low,
we were ultimately blessed with a chance.
What I'm trying to say is...
Practically zero
doesn't mean impossible, okay?
I won't pretend to understand
what you're going through.
But wanting a child is a choice
between you and your partner.
So, once you've fallen in love,
don't ponder over that question alone.
Talk it out with your partner.
Whether you mention your infertility or not
is entirely your choice.
Just like how it's your partner's choice
to decide how to respond.
I suppose so.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Everything was so delicious.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
But I'm surprised we came back here.
Why?
I love this place so much,
I may become a regular.
I'm honored you feel that way.
This is for you.
What's the occasion?
Happy birthday.
How did you know?
When I checked your license,
I happened to see your date of birth.
Oh, thank you.
Your sincerity and attitude toward work
truly inspire me.
Though I invited you today
without knowing it was your birthday,
I'm glad we could celebrate
your special day together.
Open it, if you'd like.
Then I will.
A tumbler...
It's good.
Really?
Yes!
The pasta's perfectly al dente, too.
This may be the best napolitan I've ever had.
My mother taught me
how to boil them just right.
I see.
She wants to meet you one day.
Monou...
She is celebrating today, yes?
Maybe she's getting dinner with Hirose.
Possibly.
Thank you for dinner.
And the birthday gift as well.
I'm glad you like it.
Hirose?
Monou.
Yes?
Earlier, I said I was inspired
by your work ethic.
But...
Truthfully, that's not all.
I feel as though...
we can share a future ambition together.
No, I sincerely believe it.
I won't ask for anything immediate.
But won't you look my way as well?
I can wash the rest.
It's fine, I've got it. Leave it there.
- Then could you grab the plates?
- Sure.
It just split in half.
I had fun today.
It was nice, spending time together.
I'm glad to hear it.
Really.
I had fun.
But...
Mao.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to break up.
What?
I...
I knew today was Monou's birthday.
But Mao, you're so kind.
And because you're kind,
you entertain my whims.
I didn't care if it was out of pity.
I just wanted your attention.
I guess...
I was far greedier than I thought I was.
Whenever you showed care for Monou,
I could tell the difference between us.
I thought I wouldn't mind your kindness
even if it were out of pity.
But I'm at my limit.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't ever kind to you.
I cared for you...
I rescued you...
All for my own sake.
When I was a kid,
I couldn't protect someone I cared about.
So, growing up,
I was desperate to protect
anyone I came across.
I wanted to alleviate
my regret from that day.
And now my selfish motives have hurt you.
Everything I've done...
was an insult to your feelings for me.
Then count me equally as guilty.
I knew you wouldn't let me go,
seeing how weak I was in the moment.
But I don't regret a thing.
Because...
I still wanted you, despite it all.
Mizuno...
Mao.
Will you leave things as is
with Monou?
I won't ask for anything immediate.
But won't you look my way as well?
What is it I want to do?
[Obstetrics and gynecology]
Thank you.
Take care.
You're Sui Monou's younger sister, yes?
Pardon?
Say, did your sister tell you her secret?
Her secret?
I don't think I'll meet
an individual like him again.
You love Sui, don't you?
Please make Monou happy.
She must be so jealous
you're pregnant.
I'm the worst.